June...
[MELANCHOLIC MUSIC PLAYING]
it's true that you're not
your father's true child.
You were still a baby
when he came into my life.
Your biological father...
left us and never came back.
But your father fixed
all of the paper works for you
to become his adopted child.
[SHERYN] See? Fake Rose!
But sweetie,
your father's love for you
is not fake.
Always remember that.
In his heart, you are truly
his daughter.
[MELANCHOLIC MUSIC CONTINUES]
[PING] June!
June.
What more do you want, Ping?
The truth was laid bare
in front of you.
You don't have
to pretend anymore.
You're free at last.
You could throw it all away
just like that?
All of it's fake to you?
[SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING]
- June!
- Ping!
Give June some space.
We have to talk about this
as a family first.
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
If you think that you can
finally get the Don's money,
well you're mistaken.
Because his money will go
to the foundation.
Exactly!
To the foundation
where I will be appointed
as the Chairman of the Board.
And the money will be mine!
Ours, Attorney. Don't forget.
You criminals will never win
because Toto has already
revealed everything to me.
[TOTO] I'm sorry, bro.
I'll make it up to you. I swear.
I'll send you all the evidence
that proves that Attorney
and Sheryn bribed me.
They are the masterminds
behind the sinking
of Don Nato's yacht.
And attempted murder
towards June.
Seize them!
- What? Where's your evidence?
- Attorney!
- What's this?
- Oh my god! [SHRIEKS]
Present the evidence!
Let go of me!
[ZIA] That's not true!
[MOROSE MUSIC PLAYING]